Guide to the J. DuPratt White papers, 1915-1939.
White, J. DuPratt papers, 1915-1939.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
J. DuPratt White papers, 1915-1939.
5-1-4
J. DuPratt, White 1869-1939.
15.4 cubic ft.
Letters, maps, financial documents, notes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, accounts, plans, maps, and notes relating to legal services rendered to Cornell University by the firm of White and Case and to White's membership on the Cornell Board of Trustees, particularly to work on the Buildings and Grounds, Law School, and Medical School Committees.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, accounts, plans, maps, and notes relating to legal services rendered to Cornell University by the firm of White and Case and to White's membership on the Cornell Board of Trustees, particularly to work on the Buildings and Grounds, Law School, and Medical School Committees.
SUBJECTS
Names:
White, J. DuPratt,1869-1939.; Cornell University--Buildings.; Cornell University--Finance.; Cornell University--Planning.; Cornell University--Trustees.; Cornell University.Board of Trustees.Buildings and Grounds Committee.; Cornell University.Board of Trustees.Law School Committee.; Cornell University.Board of Trustees.Medical School Committee.; White & Case.
Subjects:
Campus planning.; Legal services.
Form and Genre Terms:
Accounts.; Maps.; Plans.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Building plans and blueprints of the War Memorial and materials relating to Quill and Dagger, including those in Box 14 and 16 are restricted to permission of the University Archivist and/or the Facilities Archivist.
CONTAINER LIST
- Buildings and Grounds
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee I, Mar. 29, 1915-Oct. 1, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee II, Mar. 29, 1915-Oct. 1, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee III, Mar. 29, 1915-Oct. 1, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee I, Oct. 1, 1922-Mar. 1, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee II, Oct. 1, 1922-Mar. 1, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee III, Oct. 1, 1922-Mar. 1, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee I, Mar. 1, 1923-June. 1, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee II, Mar. 1, 1923-June. 1, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee III, Mar. 1, 1923-June. 1, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee I, June. 1, 1923-Sept. 1, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee II, June. 1, 1923-Sept. 1, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee III, June. 1, 1923-Sept. 1, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee I, Sept. 1, 1923-Jan.. 1, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee II, Sept. 1, 1923-Jan.. 1, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee III, Sept. 1, 1923-Jan.. 1, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee I, Jan. 1, 1924-July.. 1, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee II, Jan. 1, 1924-July.. 1, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee III, Jan. 1, 1924-July.. 1, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee I, July. 1, 1924-Jan. 1, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee II, July. 1, 1924-Jan. 1, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee I, Jan. 1, 1925-July 1, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee II, Jan. 1, 1925-July 1, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee III, Jan. 1, 1925-July 1, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee I, July 1, 1925-July 1, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee II, July 1, 1925-July 1, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee III, July 1, 1925-July 1, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee I, July 1, 1926-July 1, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee II, July 1, 1926-July 1, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee III, July 1, 1926-July 1, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee I, July 1, 1927-Jan 1, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee II, July 1, 1927-Jan 1, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee III, July 1, 1927-Jan 1, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee I, Jan 3, 1929-Jan 1, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee II, Jan 3, 1929-Jan 1, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee III, Jan 3, 1929-Jan 1, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee I, Jan 7, 1931-Jan 1, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee II, Jan 7, 1931-Jan 1, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee III, Jan 7, 1931-Jan 1, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee I, Jan 2, 1933-Jan 1, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee II, Jan 2, 1933-Jan 1, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee I, Jan 5, 1935-Jan 1, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee II, Jan 5, 1935-Jan 1, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee III, Jan 5, 1935-Jan 1, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee I, Jan. 1, 1937-Apr. 4, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee II, Jan. 1, 1937-Apr. 4, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee III, Jan. 1, 1937-Apr. 4, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Plan Commission and Architectural Advisory Board I, July. 1, 1922-July 1, 1925 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Plan Commission and Architectural Advisory Board II, July 1, 1922-July 1, 1925 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Plan Commission and Architectural Advisory Board I, Aug. 4, 1925-Jan. 25, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Plan Commission and Architectural Advisory Board II, Aug. 4, 1925-Jan. 25, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee. Water Supply., 1925, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee. Water Power., 1925-1928 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee. Exchange of Power., 1927-1928 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee. Miscellaneous Maps., no date (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee. Miscellaneous Maps., no date (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee. Miscellaneous Maps., no date (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee. Miscellaneous Maps., no date (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Items: Original Chart; Morse Stephens; Stables and Riding Hall for the Field Artillery Unit, ROTC; Manual for Janitor Services, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Items: Cornell Club; Building Inscriptions and Name Tablets for Campus Buildings; Building Repairs; NYS College of Agriculture Building Program, no date (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Various Maps for New Campus Roads, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Various Maps for New Campus Roads, 1924-1935 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Minutes of the Temporary Arboretum Committee, 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Memo re Apartments for Instructors and Assistant Professors, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - University Union re Commons (Willard Straight Hall) Including Plans of W.S.H., 1920, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Gymnasium, Athletic Fields, and Playing Grounds, 1902-1926 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Central Heating Plant for Cornell Campus, 1920-1923, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Booklet re the Arbitration Court of the New York Building Congress; Memo re Construction of Balch Halls, 1928-1929 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Library Construction, 1929-1936 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - University Plan Commission Reports, 1922-1925 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Chemical Laboratory at C.U. Correspondence, 1916-1917 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Chemical Laboratory at C.U. Correspondence, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Chemical Laboratory at C.U. Correspondence, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Chemical Laboratory at C.U. Correspondence, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Chemical Laboratory at C.U. Correspondence, 1922-1923 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Fund Drive and Other Miscellaneous Correspondence re Chemical Laboratory at C.U., 1915-1923 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Minutes and Correspondence re Music Building and the home Economics Building, 929-1930 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Architectural Submissions, Memos, Correspondence and Plans re Rockefeller Hall - Physics Department, 1931-1936 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Changes and Alterations re Buildings
  - Report and Drawings for the further Development of Rockefeller Hall, 1931-1936 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence and Drawings re Men's and Women's Indoor Sports Facilities, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence re the Foundation of a School of business Administration at C.U., 1915-1916 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Reports re the Foundation of a School of business Administration at C.U., 1915 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Building Alterations Needed for the University Library, 1930-1931 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Agricultural Statistics for NY State and College of Agriculture, 1910-1925 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Address by Professor Shorey at the First Convention of the Associate Alumni of C.U., No date (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Agreement between C.U. and Livingston Farrand; Also, C.U. Accepting the resignation of Jacob Gould Schurman, 1926; Feb. 1920 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Reorganization of the Engineering College at C.U., 1918 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Cornell Alumni Association, 1914-1938 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Albert Charles Murphy Estate, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Cornell University Athletic Association, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous Papers re The Veterinary Situation in NYS; Notes on the Department of Forestry at C.U.; Statement re the Proposed Science Program at C.U., No date (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Cornellian Council (Special Fund Committee), 1923 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Funds for Endowed Colleges, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Funds for Endowed Colleges, Jan. 1937-Aug. 1937 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Funds for Endowed Colleges, Sept. 1937- Dec. 1937 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Funds for Endowed Colleges, Jan. 1938-Dec. 1938 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Funds for Endowed Colleges, Jan. 1939-May. 1939 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Research Foundation, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Semi-Centennial Endowment, 1919-1921 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Clippings and Pamphlets re Cornell Fund Raising, 1920-1938 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Endowment for Physical Education Programs, 1929, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Tax Laws and Other Information, 1932-1939 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Cornell University Bequest Programs, 1932-1933 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Pamphlets re Fundraising for the University, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Estate of LaVerne Noyes, 1919, 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Semi-Centennial Endowment Campaign, 1918-1919 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Semi-Centennial Endowment Campaign Circulars, Booklets, 1918-1919 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - CU Historical Notes, The Cornellian Quarterly, 1920-1921 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Inheritance Tax Laws and Subscription Pledges, 1919-1924, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - James Parmelee Estate I, May 8, 1931-A r. 25, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - James Parmelle Estate II, May 8, 1931-Apr. 25, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Semi-Centennial Endowment Committee, Jan. 26, 1916-Jan. 1, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - James Parmelee Estate, 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Items, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Cornell General I, Jan. 3, 1928-Jan. 1, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cornell General II, Jan. 3, 1928-Jan, 1, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Cornell General, Jan. 3, 1930-Jan. 1, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Cornell General I, Jan. 1, 1931-Jan. 1, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Cornell General II, Jan. 1, 1931-Jan. 1, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Cornell General I, Jan. 6, 1932-Jan. 1, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Cornell General II, Jan. 6, 1932-Jan. 1, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Cornell General I, Jan. 2, 1933-Jan. 1, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cornell General II, Jan. 2, 1933-Jan. 1, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Cornell General I, Jan. 2, 1935-Jan. 1, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Cornell General II, Jan. 2, 1935-Jan. 1, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Cornell General, Jan. 1, 1936-Jan. 1, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Cornell General, Jan. 1, 1937-Jan. 1, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Cornell General I, Jan. 1, 1938-Aug. 1, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Cornell General II, Jan. 1, 1938-Aug. 1, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Cornell General III, Jan. 1, 1938-Aug. 1, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Association of Phi Gamma Delta and C.U. Agreement (Including Correspondence), 1920-1930 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Delta Chi Alumni Foundation (A Residence Hall for Students in Law), 1921 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Delta Chi Foundation, Dec. 16, 1920-Sept. 20, 1923 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Booklets re Student Housing at Harvard, Northwestern, and Several Other Schools, 1884, 1927-1932 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Sigma Phi and Psi Upsilon Fraternities, 1929-1934 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Sigma Phi and Psi Upsilon Fraternities, 1929-1934 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Appraisal for the Sigma Phi and Psi Upsilon Houses, Apr. 1929 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Fraternity Dormitories, Maps and Plans, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Psi Epsilon Lease; Sigma Phi Epsilon and Psi Epsilon - Subjects of Report to the Board of Trustees, Mar. 1884; Apr. 1932 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Preliminary Reports and Memos for Fraternity Housing, 1929-1930 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Minutes on the Committee of Fraternity Housing; Also, Correspondence and Reports, 1916-1932 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Telluride Association Correspondence, 1924-1930 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Memo on C.U. Property Taxation; Information re Telluride Association, 1893-1930 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Fraternity Dormitories I, Dec. 13, 1923-Jan. 1, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - raternity Dormitories II, Dec. 13, 1923-Jan. 1, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Fraternity Dormitories I, Jan. 1, 1930-Jan. 1, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Fraternity Dormitories II, Jan. 1, 1930-Jan. 1, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Fraternity Dormitories I, July. 1, 1931-July 1, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Fraternity Dormitories II, July. 1, 1931-July 1, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Fraternity Dormitories I, July. 1, 1932-Jan. 1, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Fraternity Dormitories II, July. 1, 1932-Jan. 1, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Committee on Endowment of Professorships, Oct. 18, 1920-Jan. 31, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Finance Committee, Feb. 7, 1923-Jan. 27, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Engineering College, Jan. 1, 1937-May 5, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Westchester Title - File #8, Part A - General Correspondence, Sept. 27, 1935-June 13, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Notes on Various Engineering Schools across the Country, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - York and Sawyer Plans for Engineering College, 1924-1937 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence and Memos re Sibley Family's Connection with C.U., 1920, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Shreve, Lamb, and Harmon Plans for Engineering College, 1934-1938 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Semi-Centennial Endowment Committee Reports, 1919-1920 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Legal Papers re Application of the Superintendent of Insurance of the State of New York for an Order of Liquidation for Westchester Title and Trust Company, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Per Capita Student Cost in the college of Agriculture, 1919-1921 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Clippings re NY State Insurance Department Scandal, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Memorial Professorships, 1922-1927 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Comparison of Incomes and Expenses of the various Colleges at C.U., 1919-1922 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Comparison of Incomes and Expenses of the various Colleges at C.U., 1922-1927 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Comparison of Incomes and Expenses of the various Colleges at C.U., 1932-1935 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Comparison of Incomes and Expenses of the various Colleges at C.U., 1927-1932 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Research Funds, 1932-1935 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Cornell Engineering Brochures, 1935-1938 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Adjusted Compensation of World War I Servicemen, 1924-1926 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Memos re Various C.U. Colleges, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, 1915-1921 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Jan. 1921-Feb. 1921 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Mar. 1921-Nov. 1921 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Jan. 1922-Oct. 1922 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Jan. 1922-Jan. 1923 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Feb. 1923 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Mar. 1923 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Apr.-May 1923 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, June 1923-Sept. 1923 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Oct. 1923-Feb. 1924 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Mar. 1924-June 1924 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, July 1924-Nov. 1924 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Dec. 1924-Mar. 1924 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Apr. 1925-Dec. 1925 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Jan. 1926-Dec. 1926 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Jan. 1927-Dec. 1927 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Jan. 1928-Dec. 1928 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Jan. 1929-Dec. 1929 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Jan. 1930-Dec. 1930 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Jan. 1931-Dec. 1931 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Jan. 1932-Dec. 1932 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Jan. 1933- Dec. 1934 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Jan. 1935-Dec. 1935 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Jan. 1936-Dec. 1936 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Jan. 1937-Dec. 1937 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Jan. 1938-Aug. 1938 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Cornellian Council Correspondence, Sept. 1938-June 1939 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Residence Halls at C.U. Plans and Memos, 1920-1925 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Residential Halls at C.U. Plans and Brochures, 1921-1932 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Residential Halls at C.U. Correspondence and Ackerman Reports, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Photography of Field Stones from Residential Halls Work, 1922-1923 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Dormitory Drawings at C.U., 1923-1930 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - August Heckscher Foundation Correspondence, June 1920-Oct. 1920 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence re the Construction of Balch Hall for Women, 1922-1927 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence re the Construction of Balch Hall for Women, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence re the Construction of Balch Hall for Women, 1929-1930 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Women's Dormitories, June 2, 1931-Nov. 25, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence re Men's Dormitories, 1928-1930 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence re Men's Dormitories, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence re Men's Dormitories, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence re Men's Dormitories, 1922-1923 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence re Men's Dormitories, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence re Men's Dormitories, 1925-1927 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Fraternity Dormitories, 1934-1935 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Fraternity Dormitories, 1937-1939 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Clippings re Myron Taylor Hall, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Dedication of Myron Taylor Hall, including Memos, Brochures and Correspondence, 1927-1936 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Approved Layouts for Myron Taylor Hall, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Law School and Fraternity Dormitory Correspondence; Preliminary Report for Indoor Facilities and Sports Building, 1936-1939 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Specifications of Labor and Material for Myron Taylor Hall, 1930-1931 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Law School Correspondence, 1926-1928 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Law School Correspondence, Jan. 1929-May1929 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Law School Correspondence, June 1929-Dec. 1929 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Law School Correspondence, Jan. 1930-Mar. 1930 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Law School Correspondence, Apr. 1930-June 1930 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Law School Correspondence, July 1930-Oct. 1930 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Law School Correspondence, Oct. 1930-Dec. 1930 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Law School Correspondence, Jan. 1931-Feb. 1931 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Law School Correspondence, Mar. 1931-Apr. 1931 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Law School Correspondence, May 1931-June 1931 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Law School Correspondence, July 1931-Sept. 1931 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Law School Correspondence, Oct. 1931-Dec. 1931 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Law School Correspondence, Jan. 1931-Feb. 1932 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Law School Correspondence, Mar. 1932-Apr. 1932 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Law School Correspondence, May 1932-June 1932 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Carnegie Foundation Reports, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Brochure and Reports on Pension Plan, 1920-1929 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Ruth M. Morris Loan Fund for C.U. Medical Students, 1920-1922 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, Oct. 1920-June 1921 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Information on Pension Plans, 1926-1928 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, June 1927-Dec. 1927 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, June 1928-Dec. 1929 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, Jan. 1930-Dec. 1931 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - William H. Sage Memorial Pension Fund Endowment, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Sale of Old Medical Buildings Correspondence, Nov. 1931, Jan. 1932-June 1932 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Law School Correspondence, July 1932-Sept. 1932 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence re Sale of Old Medical Buildings, Aug. 1932 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence re Sale of Old Medical Buildings Sale to N.Y. University closed Sept. 25, 1932, Sept. 1932 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence re Sale of Old Medical Buildings, Oct. 1932 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Law School Correspondence, Oct. 1932-Nov. 1932 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, Jan. 1932-Apr. 1933 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Law School Correspondence, Jan. 1933-Oct. 1933 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, May 1933-Apr. 1934 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Law School Correspondence, Mar. 1934-Dec. 1934 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, June 1934-Dec. 1935 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Law School Correspondence, Jan. 1935-Nov. 1935 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Law School Correspondence, Jan. 1936-Oct. 1936 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Law School Correspondence, Nov. 1936-Dec. 1936 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Law School Correspondence, Jan. 1937-Apr. 1937 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Law School Correspondence, Mar. 1931-Apr. 1931 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Law School Correspondence, May 1931-June 1931 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Law School Correspondence, July 1931-Sept. 1931 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Law School Correspondence, Oct. 1931-Dec. 1931 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Law School Correspondence, Jan. 1931-Feb. 1932 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Law School Correspondence, Mar. 1932-Apr. 1932 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Law School Correspondence, May 1932-June 1932 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Carnegie Foundation Reports, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Brochure and Reports on Pension Plan, 1920-1929 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Ruth M. Morris Loan Fund for C.U. Medical Students, 1920-1922 (Box 12, Folder 3)